<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Book_reviews on Reality is a Suggestion</title>
    <link>/book_reviews/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Book_reviews on Reality is a Suggestion</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="/book_reviews/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Christmas Carol by Charles Dickens</title>
      <link>/book_reviews/a_christmas_carol/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/book_reviews/a_christmas_carol/</guid>
      <description>A Christmas Carol by Charles Dickens. 01/29/18
I picked this book up on Christmas day from my parents house. It’s only about 50 pages. So, I read an average of about 1.3 pages per day. Anyway…
Ah, what a classic tale! We’re introduced to this character that is bitterer than the butt of an asparagus: Ebenezer Scrooge, whose name has since been eponymized in our society (“You’re being such a Scrooge”).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alice in Wonderland</title>
      <link>/book_reviews/alice_in_wonderland/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/book_reviews/alice_in_wonderland/</guid>
      <description>8/20/2018
“We’re all mad here,” says the Cheshire Cat to Alice. “I’m mad. You’re mad.” “How do you know I’m mad?” dear Alice wants to know. “You must be,” the cat tells her. “Or you wouldn’t have come here.”
Rather fittingly, I’ve no idea where I got this book. I only know that at some point, it was in my loft bookshelf. If I did a little investigating (between my roommates and myself) it’s possible that I’d remember it’s origins, but that’s no fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cherry by Nico Walker</title>
      <link>/book_reviews/cherry_by_nico_walker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/book_reviews/cherry_by_nico_walker/</guid>
      <description>My brother sent me this one for christmas.
Impression/Comparison This book is what Charles Bukowski would’ve written if he went to war in the 2000s instead of the Postal Service in the 60s. As I read through both stories I wondered “what the hell is the point of all this?” To both of their credits, I didn’t get the impression that either author would claim that it’s very easy to glean “a point” out of their stories (or life?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jamming by John Kao</title>
      <link>/book_reviews/jamming/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/book_reviews/jamming/</guid>
      <description>Jamming: The Art and Discipline of Business Creativity by John Kao
This is a book that tries to introduce creativity as a business commodity, and give businesspeople a rough guide for intentionally bringing creativity into their companies/personal workflows. Kao likens business creativity to jazz. The comparison between business (or any creative process really) and jazz is my favorite aspect of this book.
“Jazz- like business- implies a series of balancing acts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Persepolis</title>
      <link>/book_reviews/persepolis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/book_reviews/persepolis/</guid>
      <description>Persepolis by Marjane Satrapi February 2019
Teta Anne sent me this one for christmas. I crushed it on the plane ride to Denver.
The Medium On one hand, a graphic novel (told through a child’s eyes) is a limiting way to learn about a topic as complicated as the Iranian revolution. On the other hand, it makes the delivery of such a story easily accessible and entertaining.
How the medium was limiting: For the first few sections I found myself flipping back and forth between the introduction (which provided 2 pages of historical context), and the story to try to figure out what the hell was going on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pincher Martin by William Golding</title>
      <link>/book_reviews/pincher_martin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/book_reviews/pincher_martin/</guid>
      <description>Pincher Martin by William Golding 05/23/2018
I found this book in a ski bag I hadn’t touched in a couple years. The last Golding book I read was Lord of the Flies on a ski trip at Tremblant with Dad in ~2010. I’m beginning to see a pattern emerge… I think I’ve been writing these reviews as if the reader has already read the book. In any case: SPOILER ALERT!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Soonish</title>
      <link>/book_reviews/soonish/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/book_reviews/soonish/</guid>
      <description>Soonish: Ten Emerging Technologies That’ll Improve and/or Ruin Everything By Zach and Kelly Weinersmith
This book is written by the author of my favorite webcomic, Saturday Morning Breakfast Cereal, along with his wife. So, I had to get the book when I heard it was being written. It’s full of humorous analogies used to explain scientific phenomena, a single-panel comic every couple pages, and not to mention, some actual information/speculations about the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Sun Also Rises</title>
      <link>/book_reviews/the_sun_also_rises/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/book_reviews/the_sun_also_rises/</guid>
      <description>The story follows Jake, a young (~30) expat in France the 1920s. He and his friends all seem to love the same girl, Brett. Jake lives his normal partying/working life in Paris. He smooches Brett. Brett can’t be with him, but oh wouldn’t it be lovely if she could. They would have such a nice time together, they both agree. But oh no it cannot be, she declares. Jake then goes on a trip to Spain.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>